

Mahsa Zakeri Front-end Developer

⊠ mahsazakeri1377@gmail.com

♥ Tehran,Iran

in @in/mahsa-zakeri

\(+98 935 293 0991

ABOUT ME

Creative and forward-thinking front-end developer with over 3 years of experience in building and maintaining responsive websites with ReactJS. Equipped with a history of success in continuously identifying and meeting the technical needs of the project through innovative innovation. Currently, I'm working on 3 projects at the same time and seeking new opportunities to improve my skills and go further.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GardeshPay

Front End Developer (May 2022 - Present)

- Design and establish user-friendly websites, resulting in a 25% increase in user clicks and subsequently 13% in customer purchases.
- Assisted with the bug fix and support of the existing secure websites like <u>Channelead</u>, <u>Apro</u>, and <u>Bedcasting</u> using Angular.
- Implemented new features based on user feedback, Enhanced a 15% increase in user experience.
- Migrated a multi-page user experience into a single-page app, improving customer engagement by 10%.

ProShot

Front End Team Lead (July 2021 - May 2022)

- Managed re-factoring process and improve efficiency, restructured communication flow among 3 departments.
- Expand and developed the PalPhone project and increase performance by up to 40%.
- Directing or conducting website updates.
- Tecnical interviwed with more than 50 people.
- Conducted workload assessments and devised new operational processes that led to a 40% increase in productivity.
- Customized 5 features and as a result market team sold 13% more.
- Documenting solution architecture for the high-profile progressive web application.
- standardizing the way of development amongst different projects and mitigating code duplicity.
- Ensuring proper documentation and reports in all stages of product life cycles.

Adrian System

Front End Developer (December 2020 - July 2021)

- Designed an ecommerce shopping website focused on user reviews.
- Re-design a government project and cut down paperwork up to 70%.

Shaya Smart Solution

Junior Front End Developer (September 2018 - August 2019)

- Coded 2 control admin panels, adtrace, and kavan.
- Collected data for an AI project which led to a 40% increase in team time.

SKILLS

- Expert in front-end development using React.JS.
- Hands-on Redux, Angular, RxJs, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Material-UI, AntDesign, Bootstrap, Figma, Adobe XD, Scss, Git, and Responsive web design.
- Familiar with WebRTC, Socket.io.

EDUCATION

LANGUAGE

Iran Informatic institute

Associate Software Engineer

- Teaching Assistant in web designing course.
- Created an admin control panel for checking class time used by both teachers and students.

LANGUAGE	
English	
German	